<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="assetNode" name="assetNode" security="5" allowsDefaultBootModule="false" type="1">
    <portsForCrack val="9001"/>
    <ports>22</ports>
    
    <adminPass pass="You'reGonnaLoveThis,TrustMe" />

<!--Mission breifings for E1 and E2-->
    <file path="home/tasks" name="01_Getting_Started.txt">
This is a basic deployment of Hacknet designed by us, your
friendly international Will Council. As a reminder, we would
rather that you not share this operating system or any of its
components.
Not yet.

Your current x-server.sys provides basic functionality.
You are able to backup, shutdown, see your IP, connect to your
email server, and access a barebones command shell.
You also have a few programs on your system under the /bin folder.

However, this meagre set of tools is far from complete.
Find a complete x-server.sys. From what we know, there are
a few organizations that should be in possesion of one.

We recommend a pen and some paper to keep track of the
networks you encounter, and other useful info, for now.

Don't worry, we WILL help you along.

222.51.39.138</file>
<file path="home/tasks" name="02_Well_Done.txt">
So you've not only slipped through a corporate network
without a trace, but you've bested a fellow hacker at
his own game?

Consider us impressed, #PLAYERNAME#!

Now, unless hackerman got better at hiding things recently,
you should have found one of his hitlists on his machine.
Only one address should be of any significance.

Get going, WILL you?
</file>

<file path="home/tasks" name="03_Next_steps.txt">
Well done.
You should now have an encrypted x-server.sys.
All the same, it IS encrypted. Worry not, we know exactly
the encryption algorithm used and the company that
developed it.

The DEC suite of tools you'll need don't seem to be publicly
available right now, so we'll have to resort to going through
their corporate network.

Connect to 79.5.101.1 for an administrator's home network.
You WILL find the information you need to put yourself on the
whitelist for the DEC network so you can proceed.
</file>

<file path="home/tasks" name="04_DEC_Access.txt">
Brilliant.
Now that you have whitelisted yourself for the DEC network,
it's time to dig a little deeper.
However, this next inner layer is far more formidable than
the outer one you have already bested.

We have a gift to help out out: a Remote Code Execution script,
courtesy of a council member whose specialty is getting code
to run where it shouldn't.

Upload /home/qRCEsuite.exe to a filedrop server. It retrieves
a login for the server through what can only be described as
black magic crafted with underappreciated genius.

You should be able to find the source control server in that network.
There should be two DEC utility programs there (or somewhere thereabouts)
that you WILL upload to the public drop server, IP below:
10.10.10.100
</file>

<file path="home/tasks" name="05_One_of_many.txt">
Congratulations on nabbing those programs. You've managed to make
it this far even with the rather disadvantageous circumstances.

As a courtesy, we'll save you the hassle of trying to bruteforce
the encryption on the file. Our own boxes spent enough
CPU cycles cracking the algorithm as it is.

You'll find the decrypted x-server on your system at
/sys/x-server_0.sys

Delete your old x-server and rename x-server_0.sys to x-server.sys
Then connect to our cracked license server below. Yes, this build has
DRM for x-servers.

137.74.187.101
</file>

<file path="home/tasks" name="06_Alright.txt">
How does your new environment look? Pretty neat,
eh?

Your install isn't complete, however. There's one
more graphical element slot left in the interface
and a few important cracker programs missing.

For now, you've met the preliminary requirements
for joining the main Will board. Further help can
be found there.

WILLcome aboard.

137.74.187.103
</file>

<!--Custom/Important files-->
<file path="home" name="qRCEsuite.exe">#BINARY#</file>
<file path="bin" name="ReadMe.txt">
Here's a quick how-to for those unfamilliar:

>SQLInject and WebServerWorm are two all too common crackers.
Like many others you'll come across, all you need to do is call them 
with the port number of the service they are designed for
(nmap will help with that) and in time, they'll bust that port
wide open for a PortHack.

>DNotes is nifty, it'll dump all the notes you make with addNote to
stdout, so you can read them in the terminal.

>You can use ps to keep track of what's running, and nmap to keep
track of what's open on the host machine.

Use wisely, friend of WILL.
</file>

<customthemefile path="sys" name="x-server_0.sys" themePath="Themes/AllBlack.xml"/>

<!-- Saved closings
-
Now find us.

We WILL be waiting.
-
We WILL keep in touch.
-
GoodWILL towards a fellow hacker.
-
-->

<!--Programs. All of them.-->
<file path="bin" name="SSHCrack.exe">#SSH_CRACK#</file>
<file path="bin" name="FTPBounce.exe">#FTP_CRACK#</file>
<file path="bin" name="WebServerWorm.exe">#WEB_CRACK#</file>
<file path="bin" name="SMTPOverflow.exe">#SMTP_CRACK#</file>
<file path="bin" name="SQLBufferOverflow.exe">#SQL_CRACK#</file>
<file path="bin" name="HexClock.exe">#HEXCLOCK_EXE#</file>
<file path="bin" name="Clock.exe">#CLOCK_PROGRAM#</file>
<file path="bin" name="Decypher.exe">#DECYPHER_PROGRAM#</file>
<file path="bin" name="DECHead.exe">#DECHEAD_PROGRAM#</file>
<file path="bin" name="KBTPortTest.exe">#MEDICAL_PROGRAM#</file>
<file path="bin" name="ThemeChanger.exe">#THEMECHANGER_EXE#</file>
<file path="bin" name="eosDeviceScan.exe">#EOS_SCANNER_EXE#</file>
<file path="bin" name="SecurityTracer.exe">#SECURITYTRACER_PROGRAM#</file>
<file path="bin" name="Tracekill.exe">#TRACEKILL_EXE#</file>
<file path="bin" name="RTSPCrack.exe">#RTSP_EXE#</file>
<file path="bin" name="ESequencer.exe">#EXT_SEQUENCER_EXE#</file>
<file path="bin" name="OpShell.exe">#SHELL_OPENER_EXE#</file>
<file path="bin" name="TorrentStreamInjector.exe">#TORRENT_EXE#</file>


</Computer>
